The main advantage of the AsyncTask is that you get
AsyncTask(异步任务)的主要优点就是你可以
to focus on your app logic, what you need to do
专注于你的应用程序的逻辑，你只需要知道在
on the background thread, and what you need to do when
背景线程中做什么，和当她
it comes back to the main thread. You don't have to
回到主线程时需要做什么。你就不用
worry about the details of threads and handlers. Of the methods
担心线程和处理程序的详细信息了。关于
that I showed you, only doInBackground is required to be implemented.
我向你展示的方法中，只有doInBackground是被要求要实现的。
onPostExecute is optional as well as some other methods. For each
onPostExecute则是和其他的方法一样是随意的。对于每一个
method, tell us whether it's on the main or background thread.
方法，告诉我们她是在主线程还是在背景线程。
You have a 50% chance of getting each one correct or a 100%
你有50%的机会猜对或者就是100%
if you actually go check the java doc, so go do that now.
如果你真的看了java，那就现在赶紧去做吧。